https://wrinstitute.org/wp-content/themes/wrinstitute/about/legal/

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING LEGAL INFORMATION CAREFULLY. THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS HAVE CHANGED SINCE THE LAST VISIT TO OUR SITE. BY USING THIS SITE, YOU INDICATED ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS CONDITIONS, THEN DO NOT USE THIS SITE.
TERMS AND CONDITIONS
The Will Rogers Motion Picture Pioneers Foundation (WRMPPF) maintains this web site as a service to its clients, donors, potential and other interested parties. Please visit us frequently and browse our pages. Downloads are subject to the terms and conditions set out below.
USERS/PARTICIPANTS
We do not discriminate on the basis of age, race, national origin, gender, and sexual orientation.No person under the age of 13 should use the site. We strongly encourage all parents and guardians to monitor the Internet use of their children. Use of the site by any user shall be deemed to be a representation that the user if 13 years of age or older.
TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS & RESTRICTIONS
This site, and materials on the site, including, but not limited to, images, illustrations, posts, audio clips, and video clips (the “materials”) are the property of WRMPPF and its affiliates and licensors and are protected from unauthorized copying and dissemination by copyrights that are owned or licensed by WRMPPF and by the copyright law, trademark law, international conventions and other intellectual property laws. By way of example, and not as a limitation, WRMPPF is a registered trademark under the applicable laws of the United States and other countries. All other logos or product names are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. You may not reproduce, perform, create derivative works from, republish, upload, post, transmit, or distribute in any way whatsoever any materials from www.wrinstitute.org, any bulletin board, or any other web site owned or operated by WRMPPF without the prior written permission of WRMPPF. However, you may download or make on copy of the materials, and other downloadable items displayed on the site, for personal, non-commercial home use only, provided all copy right and other notices contained in the materials are left intact. Any modification of the materials, or any portion thereof, or use of the materials for any other purpose constitute and infringement of WRMPPF copyrights and other proprietary rights. Use of these materials on any other web site or other networked computer environment is prohibited without prior written permission from WRMPPF.
Nothing contained on this site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use this site or any information displayed on this site, throughout the use of framing otherwise, except: (a) as expressly permitted by these terms and conditions; or (b) with the prior written permission of WRMPPF of such third party that may own the trademark or copyright of information displayed on the site.
Copyright and Trademark Information ”2013 Will Rogers Motion Picture Pioneers Foundation. All Rights Reserved.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
WRMPPF is not responsible for the content of any site that may be linked to or from www.wrinstitute.org, or any bulletin board associated with WRMPPF. These links are provided for your convenience only and you access them at your own risk. Any other web site accessed from this site is independent from WRMPPF, and WRMPPF has no control over the content of that other web site. In addition, a link to any other web sites does not imply that WRMPPF endorses or accepts responsibility for the content or use of such other web site.
NO IMPLIED ENDORSEMENTS
In no event shall any reference to any third party or third party product or service be construed as an approval, guarantee or endorsement by WRMPPF of that third party of any product or service provided by a third party.
PRIVACY ISSUES
WRMPPF is concerned about privacy matters for its customers. Please review our Privacy Statement.
DISCLAIMERS AND INDEMNITY
By using the site and/or posting materials, you agree to indemnity WRMPPF, its officers, directors, employees, successors, agents, and affiliates for any and all claims, damage, losses and causes of action (including attorneys’ fees and court costs) arising out of or relating to your breach or alleged breach of this Agreement (including without limitation, claims made by third parties for infringement of intellectual property rights), or for any content that is provided by you. You agree to cooperate fully as reasonably required in WR defense and/or settlement of any claim. WRMPPF reserves the right to assume that exclusive control over the defense and settlement of any matter subject to indemnification by you.
This information contained in this site is for general guidance on topics selected by WRMPPF. Such information is provided on a blind-basis, without any knowledge as to your industry, identity or specific circumstances. The application and impact of relevant laws will vary from jurisdiction to jurisdiction. There may also be delays, omissions, or inaccuracies in information contained in this site. The information on this site is provided with the understanding that WRMPPF and various authors and publishers’ providing such information does not constitute the rendering of legal, accounting, tax, career or other professional advice or services. As such, information on this site should not be relied upon or used as a substitute or consultation with professional advisors.
WRMPPF SITE MAY CONTAIN FACTS, VIEWS, OPINIONS, STATEMENTS, AND RECOMMENDATIONS OF THIRD-PARTY INDIVIDUALS AND ORGANIZATIONS. WILL ROGERS INSTITUTE DOES NOT REPRESENT OR ENDORSE THE ACCURACY, CURRENTNESS, OR RELIABILITY OF ANY ADVICE, OPINION, STATEMENT, RECOMMENDATIONS, OR OTHER INFORMATION DISPLAYED, UPLOADED, OR DISTRIBUTED THROUGH THE SITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ANY RELIANCE ON ANY SUCH OPINION, STATEMENT, RECOMMENDATIONS, OR INFORMATION WILL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. FURTHERMORE, WILL ROGERS INSTITUTE DOES NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE QUALITY OF, OR ACCURACY OF ADVERTISEMENTS FOR, ANY MERCHANDISE, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED OR PROVIDED BY ITS ALLIES OR SUPPLIERS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE WRMPPF SERVICE.
THE MATERIALS ON THE SITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASES AND WITHOUT EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. WILL ROGERS INSTITUTE MAKES NO WARRANTY AS TO THE QUALITY, ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, AND VALIDITY OF ANY MATERIALS ON THE SITE AND DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONALITY CONTAINED ON THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER(S) THAT MAKE IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
Where applicable law does not allow the exclusions of implied warranties, the foregoing exclusions may not apply to you.
EXCLUSIONS OF DAMAGES
NEITHER WILL ROGERS MOTION PICTURE PIONEERS FOUNDATION, NOR ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTOR, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUCCESSORS, OR AFFILIATES ARE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER INDIRECT DAMAGES OR FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF DATA OR LOSS OF USE DAMAGES, THAT RESULT FROM THE INABILITY TO USE, THIS SITE OR THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS WEB SITE, EVEN IF WILL ROGERS INSTITUTE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
IN NO EVENT SHALL WILL ROGERS INSTITUTE TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FROM ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION RESULTING FROM YOU USE OF THIS SITE OR PARTICIPATION IN THE WILL ROGERS INSTITUTE’S SERVICE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO NEGLIGENCE), STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EXCEED THE MAXIMUM AMOUNT OF FUNDS IN THE MEMBER ACCOUNT AT THE TIME THE CLAIM ARISES.
JURISDICTION
WRMPPF operates the site from its offices within the United States. WRMPPF makes no representation that information on this site is appropriate or available for use outside the United States. Those who choose to access this site from outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
When an individual provides Personal Information to the WRMPPF, the WRMPPF may use the Personal Information for its programs, research and fund-raising. The WRMPPF will suppress the use of an individual’s Personal Information if requested by that individual.
SPECIFIC REQUIREMENTS
All Personal Information collected on individuals will be kept confidential and in a secure environment – not shared, we do not sell or rent our list.
COMMENT, COMPLAINTS AND QUESTIONS
We welcome your feedback about the site. However, any comments, ideas, notes, messages, suggestions or other communications sent to the site shall be and remain the exclusive property of WRMPPF, and we may use all such communications in any manner, including reproducing, disclosing and publishing such communications, all without compensation to you.
Should you have any questions or complaints regarding these terms and conditions, please contact us toll-free at
(888) 994-3863.
Why Donate?
Employer Matching
